Previously on
Two and a Half Men:
Larry, where can
I put this poop?
This is my sister Gretchen.
She just moved here.
Gretchen, this is
Jeff Strongman.
We have a half hour
till I have to go meet Larry.
I really like Gretchen.
I'm-I'm not gonna cheat on her.
Gretchen is coming over tonight.
When I get back,
I don't want to see Gretchen.
BARRY:
You know,
if I had a place to sleep here,
my apartment would be free.
You had me at "free."
♪ Men. ♪
(phone rings)
Oh, I'm sorry.
I have to take this.
It's my partner from China.
No problem.
Hello?
Lan mao shi zai wuding shang.
Wow.
No, I'm on hold.
I'm just making stuff up.
(harp playing)
(theme music playing)
Honey, I'm home!
Hi, dear.
How was your
day, darling?
Did you write some
new commercials?
I sure did, Mother.
In six months,
everyone in America
will be smoking
refreshing cigarettes.
Or, as I like
to call them,
healthy flavor sticks.
Kids, your
father's home!
(children cheering)
Look at all
my little Schmidts!
And I pushed every one of
those Schmidts out of me.
Hey, kids,
if you eat all your dinner,
Daddy's gonna give
a healthy flavor stick
to each and every one of you.
(children cheering)
Hi, Dad.
I clogged
the toilet again.
And I ain't cleanin' it up!
Oh, Berta. Oh, Berta.
Oh, Berta.
KATE:
Walden.
Walden.
Walden?
Oh, s...
Sorry. (clears throat)
I was daydreaming.
We were married,
and we had seven kids,
and they all loved cigarettes.
Okay, that's the last margarita
for you.
So, I have good news
and I have bad news.
Oh. Is the good news
that we're gonna have sex
and the bad news that we can
only do it five times?
The bad news is I have to go
to San Francisco, like, now.
Wow.
And the good news is,
once I take care
of this business,
I can stay here
for a few more days.
Hmm, then I can take care
of your bidness.
Oh, hey, Kate.
I see you're still
as beautiful as ever.
Alan.
I see you're still as...
here as ever.
So we're both doing well.
Okay, I got to go pack my stuff
so I can leave.
Mmm.
I'll take "phrases Alan Harper
will never say" for $500.
She's leaving already?
Oh, I hope she doesn't
use that bathroom.
I clogged the
toilet again.
No, she's only gone
for a couple days.
And then I'm gonna ask her
to marry me.
Wait, married?
Well, isn't that
a little fast?
(groans)
Walden, you're always jumping
into these kind of things,
and you...
You can still live here.
Mazel tov!
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Two and a Half Men 11x19 ♪
Lan Mao Shi Zai Wuding Shang
Original Air Date on
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ Men. ♪
Hey. Hi.
Hey.
What you guys doing?
I am taking Jenny to the movies.
Okay, you're
not taking me.
Taking me implies
we're going on a date.
I'm a lesbian. If
anything, I'm taking you
'cause you can't get into an
R-rated movie by yourself.
Hey. Hold on.
Uh, before you go,
which one
of these engagement rings
do you think Kate would like?
W... what?
You're gonna ask her
to marry you?
She's only been back
for one day.
Yeah. She's the one.
(chuckles) Do you know how rare
it is to meet the one?
Let alone have it happen
every six months?
No, no. This is...
this is different.
I-I am... really in love
with Kate.
Okay, I really love
my life-size anime doll,
but it would be a little weird
if I married it.
Right?
Look, Walden, you're in love
with being in love.
You live like you're
in a romantic comedy.
You know who's gonna play you
in the movie about your life?
Julia Roberts.
Just... do what my dad did.
Don't buy the cow if you can get
the lactating stripper to
give you the milk for free.
Come on, Barry,
let's go.
You know who would play me
and you in the movie?
Tom Hanks and Meg Ryan.
I'll be either one.
(sighs)
Hey, Charlie.
It's me, Walden.
We... never met, but I'm the guy
who took your place.
Thanks for giving up your house.
I guess you didn't really
give it up-- you died.
You'd have to be on crack
to give up all this.
Anyway, I...
Is Jenny right?
I mean, do I fall in love
too fast?
Come on, Charlie,
talk to me.
At least show me a sign.
(chuckles)
Yeah.
That's what I thought.
(knocking)
(yelps)
(thunder rumbles)
♪ Men. ♪
Here, try my
famous guacamole.
Oh, what makes it famous?
I don't know. It's...
really good
and everybody likes it.
I didn't think
you'd actually call me on it.
Do you have any
famous recipes?
Well, there's the-the Strongman
family meatloaf.
You'll have to make that for me.
Uh, the recipe died
with my grandmother.
Oh.
We'd always say,
"Write it down, write it down."
And she'd say...
(European accent): "Tomorrow."
One day, your tomorrows
run out.
Oh, Nana Strongman.
Aw.
Every day, I learn something new
about my Jeff.
(chuckles)
You and me both.
I wish we could be
together every day.
Oh, what would that be like?
Well, let's put it this way:
The Strongman meat
would not be loafing.
Move in with me.
Seriously?
You make this place a home.
When you're not here,
this apartment feels
like it belongs
to somebody else.
So what do you say?
I say yes.
Oh, my God, that's great!
But I insist
on paying half the rent.
I love you.
Cash only.
♪ Men. ♪
Can I help you?
Hey, sorry to bother you. I...
I've been hiking all day, and
I saw you had a hose out here,
and I was wondering if I could
fill up my water bottle.
I have a hose?
Yeah.
Bottom of the stairs.
Good for me.
Uh, I... actually, I have
filtered water in the kitchen.
Oh, I kind of had my heart set
on dirty hose water,
but if you insist.
(angelic choir singing)
Should I...
I'm sorry, what?
(chuckles)
Sh-Should I wipe my feet?
I-I don't want
to track beach sand into your...
...house sand?
Oh, no. That's-that's not sand.
That's the remains of the guy
who used to live here.
You know what, maybe I'll just
use the hose outside. It's fine.
No, no, no, no.
No, it's not like that.
He gets spilled all the time.
At this point, he's mostly lint.
I'm Walden.
Vivian.
That's a beautiful name.
Thank you. My parents got it
from that '70s show.
What was it called? Maude.
Ah.
Yeah.
Wow, this is...
this is quite a place.
(chuckles)
Your desk is backwards.
Excuse me?
Well, you have this
beautiful view of the ocean,
and yet your desk
is facing the wall with...
a picture of the ocean on it.
Yeah. It's... actually,
it's-it's the Atlantic.
(chuckles)
It's an inside joke.
For myself.
(thunder rumbles)
Uh, you know what,
I better fill up and get going.
But it's, like... it's really
starting to come down out there.
It's just a little water.
I'm not gonna melt.
It's not like I'm
the Wicked Witch of the West.
I mean, you could wait it out
here if you want.
We could have dinner together.
I'll-I'll order delivery.
Really?
Wow. Uh, yeah.
That'd be great.
Great.
Okay.
(chuckles)
Thank you.
You know, I-I got to ask,
do you always invite strangers
into your home?
Oh, no.
Usually they invite themselves.
♪ Men. ♪
I am so excited to
move in with you.
Hey, on top of paying
half the rent,
I insist on paying
half the utilities.
Thank you. By the way,
there's also a security deposit,
a cleaning deposit
and the groceries
you've already eaten half of.
But we'll figure that out later.
We're gonna have so much fun.
(chuckles)
Oh. Oh. If this is gonna get
any more physical,
I got to go freshen up.
You mean poop?
I love you so much.
Oh, hey, if, uh,
the pizza guy shows up,
I don't have any money.
Hey, that's my line!
My wallet's on the counter.
Thanks.
(slow motion):
Wait...!
Who's Alan Harper?
A guy who no longer has to poop.
♪ Men. ♪
So, what's your deal,
Walden?
Good-looking guy, rich,
Malibu beach house.
I bet you only date
hot actresses.
God, no.
I'd never date an actress.
They're all crazy.
I'm sure they're not all crazy.
Trust me. They are.
I don't get
this whole fascination
with celebrities anyway.
I mean, who cares
who's dating whom
or who's engaged to who
or who has a sex tape
that no one will ever, ever see?
I know. But I have to say
I am a sucker for anything
having to do
with Brangelina or Kimye.
Yeah, I have no idea
what that means.
I thought we were eating Kimye.
What, have you been hiding under
a rock for the last few years?
No, but I have climbed a few.
I was a Sherpa in Nepal.
Yeah.
And I...
I drove cattle in Argentina.
And I, uh... Oh, I used
to give safari tours in Africa.
And, once, I was an assistant
manager at a Hot Dog on a Stick
in Pittsburgh.
I love hot dogs.
(laughs)
I've never even thought
about doing stuff like that.
I mean, although I did
once sit in the splash section
at SeaWorld without a poncho.
Well, then you'd be perfect
for my next adventure.
Crewing on a sailboat
to Polynesia.
Wow.
A sailboat to Polynesia.
So what island do you
want to hit first?
As long as we're together,
it doesn't matter.
(gasping)
That was a close one.
I barely caught you guys.
I'm still living
with you, right?
Whoa...
VIVIAN (distant):
Walden.
Walden.
Huh?
Which one do you want?
Right now I want both.
Oh, here. (laughs)
Oh.
"A new love awaits you."
Wow.
Mine says,
"Try our gluten-free wontons."
♪ Men. ♪
Okay, uh, you asked, uh,
"Who is Alan Harper""
And you deserve
the truth.
My real name is Alan Harper.
I-I used to date Lyndsey,
but when she broke up with me,
I wanted to meet
her new boyfriend, Larry,
but I didn't want him
to know that it was me,
so I created a fake persona,
Jeff Strongman,
but then Larry and I
became real friends,
and then you came along,
and I really liked you,
and everything was perfect
until you picked up my wallet
to pay for the pizza,
which reinforces my one rule:
"Never offer
to pay for anything!"
Wow. So nothing I know
about you is real?
My-my feelings for you are real.
And I was telling the truth
when I said
I wanted you to live with me.
What about your son?
Oh, oh, that-that wasn't a lie.
I have a son,
just not the guy you met.
M.I.T.?
L.I.E.
Anything else?
I take regular condoms, and I
put them in the Magnum box.
Yeah, I kind of figured that.
All right, good-bye, Jeff.
Alan. Whatever your name is.
Please, Gretchen, Gretchen,
don't go, don't go.
I really do care
for you. Oh!
Gretchen, come back!
You have the pizza coupon!
♪ Men. ♪
Wow, look at you.
Now you can look at the ocean
and watch porn at the same time.
Oh, I don't like looking
at naked women.
That didn't
come out right.
I use this computer
for work.
In fact, it's what paid
for this view.
This view is free.
Everything you say
is like a bumper sticker.
Well, I'm just gonna
keep on truckin', then!
Hey, don't forget to coexist.
You know, it's with all
the religious symbols?
The star of David
and the fish.
It's a bumper sticker.
Never mind.
All right, where-where...
where you headed?
Carbon Canyon tonight,
and then the...
the road is open,
and so is my mind.
(gasps) Ooh, that could be
a bumper sticker.
Hey, uh, why don't you give me
your number?
We'll have to stay in touch.
I don't have a phone.
That is awesome.
So I guess this is good-bye.
I-I guess so.
Hey, thanks for letting me
crash on your couch
and for the hot shower.
By the way, your staff
is so attentive.
I mean, that Barry kid
checked up on me,
like, five times
during the night.
All right, you know,
I-I don't usually say this
to people in this house, but...
if you want,
you can stay longer.
You're very sweet, Walden,
but, uh, I gotta get going.
Enjoy your view.
(chuckles)
Hey, Vivian.
Yeah?
Are you gonna be okay?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
I mean, this is...
this is what I do.
Okay.
Walden?
Yeah?
Are you gonna be okay?
I do...
think I'm gonna be okay.
♪ Men. ♪
Okay, I think I, uh,
got all my stuff.
Okay, that is my lamp.
Oh. Oh, yeah, yeah,
but I put a new bulb in it.
So, you know, I'll just wait
till this one blows out,
then I'll shoot it
right back to you.
Okay. Or...
(doorbell rings)
I'll be back for you.
Gretchen?
I'm glad you're here.
I realized the only thing
I actually know about you
is where you live.
Well...
Oh, my God, is everything
about you a lie?
Are you even cheap?
I am cheap.
Two of the four windows
in my car are garbage bags.
Look... look, I know
I was an idiot,
but-but what I said before
about how much I care about you,
I-I meant that.
But... you know,
I-I understand if you want
nothing to do with me.
That's why I'm here.
Look, I made my share
of mistakes
when my husband left me.
I know how hurtful it can be.
I know how crazy you can become.
I mean, I'm sure you Googled me
and saw my mug shots online.
Uh, no. Um...
Well, don't freak out.
I was innocent.
According to the state
of Illinois.
The point is,
we all have secrets.
So, are you saying that we can
get back together?
I'm saying I would like
to break up with Jeff Strongman
and get to know Alan Harper.
Really? Oh, that's great.
But-but first, I'd like
one last moment with Jeff.
Jeff?
Yes?
Screw you.
Oh, God!
(groans)
Oh, are you okay, Alan?
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, you.
Hey, you're back.
So, I've got good news
and I've got great news.
The good news is,
I did work it out
so I could stay a few more days.
Oh.
And the great news is,
I took my underwear off
in the car.
Hey, um...
(grunts, stammers)
Listen, we need...
we need to talk.
Awfully serious for someone
who just got hit in the face
with a thong.
Here's the thing.
While you were gone,
I met someone.
What?
I mean, nothing happened
physically.
It's just, I can't stop thinking
about her,
and it's made me question
everything,
including my sanity
and my interior
decorating instincts.
Are you saying that you want
to be with this girl now?
I don't know what I want.
I just, I know I have
to pursue this.
Wow.
I'm-I'm-I'm sorry.
I-I never meant to hurt you.
I don't feel the same.
(groans)
♪ Men. ♪
Hi.
Hi-ya!
(groans)
Oh...
Oh, they had just
dropped back down!
Walden, what are you doing here?
(groans)
Remember how you asked me
if I was gonna be okay?
I don't think I am.
Is it because I just kicked you
in the balls?
There's that.
Uh, but before I met you,
I was very close to asking
another woman to marry me.
But then I didn't...
because I couldn't stop thinking
of you.
So, you came here to tell me
that you dumped your girlfriend,
sweep me off my feet,
and the two of us would,
what, sail off
into the sunset together?
Yes?
You don't even know me.
Okay... I know you enough
to know that I want
to know you more.
Walden, stop it.
I'm just a stranger who wanted
to drink from your hose.
Okay, that didn't... that didn't
really come out right.
Look, I know
I don't know you
very well, but I feel like
you're the type of guy
who falls in love easily.
You know me perfectly!
That's exactly who I am.
I... look, we're soul mates.
Soul mates aren't made in a day.
Oh, that's another
great bumper sticker.
Walden, you're a great guy,
but we lead
two very different lives.
Did I mention
that I have a plane
and I can take you anywhere
you want to go?
Do you see?
You want to fly over everything.
For you, it's all about
the destination.
For me, the journey
is the destination.
Okay, are you writing
these down?
Go home, Walden.
(stammering)
But I-I walked
four miles to get here
in the dark.
In the woods!
I don't even know
if I can find my way home.
Maybe I should just stay
with you.
(alarm chirps)
Ah, dude, there's your car.
♪ Men. ♪
Here you go, sweetie.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry
I freaked out on you.
It's not your fault.
I should've known better.
VIVIAN:
I'm sorry, too.
I should have never let you go.
Well, you're both here now...
and I'm ready to enjoy the view.
You want us to kiss, Walden?
Yeah, kiss each other.
Do it.
Kiss each other.
Well, it is his house.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man